{"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["dž",""],"osnova":"deter","osnova2":"ent","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["dž",""],"osnova":"","osnova2":"amija","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["dž",""],"osnova":"","osnova2":"em","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["dž",""],"osnova":"","osnova2":"emper","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["dž",""],"osnova":"","osnova2":"ep","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["dž",""],"osnova":"","osnova2":"eparac","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["dž",""],"osnova":"","osnova2":"ungla","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["dž",""],"osnova":"ho","osnova2":"a","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["dž",""],"osnova":"naru","osnova2":"ba","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["dž",""],"osnova":"pan","osnova2":"a","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["dž",""],"osnova":"pi","osnova2":"ama","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["dž",""],"osnova":"u","osnova2":"benik","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ",""],"osnova":"an","osnova2":"eo","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ",""],"osnova":"doga","osnova2":"aj","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ",""],"osnova":"doga","osnova2":"ati se","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ",""],"osnova":"","osnova2":"ak","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ",""],"osnova":"","osnova2":"avao","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ",""],"osnova":"","osnova2":"ur","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ",""],"osnova":"gospo","osnova2":"a","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ",""],"osnova":"gospo","osnova2":"ica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ",""],"osnova":"gra","osnova2":"evina","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ",""],"osnova":"grož","osnova2":"e","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ",""],"osnova":"izme","osnova2":"u","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ",""],"osnova":"kra","osnova2":"a","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ",""],"osnova":"le","osnova2":"a","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ",""],"osnova":"ma","osnova2":"ioničar","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ",""],"osnova":"ma","osnova2":"ioničarka","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ",""],"osnova":"me","osnova2":"u","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ",""],"osnova":"novoro","osnova2":"enče","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ",""],"osnova":"odre","osnova2":"ivati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ",""],"osnova":"oru","osnova2":"e","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ",""],"osnova":"poga","osnova2":"ati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ",""],"osnova":"poro","osnova2":"aj","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ",""],"osnova":"posu","osnova2":"e","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ",""],"osnova":"posu","osnova2":"ivati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ",""],"osnova":"ro","osnova2":"ak","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ",""],"osnova":"ro","osnova2":"akinja","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ",""],"osnova":"ro","osnova2":"endan","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ",""],"osnova":"ro","osnova2":"enje","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ",""],"osnova":"sme","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ",""],"osnova":"strojovo","osnova2":"a","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ",""],"osnova":"sva","osnova2":"a","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ",""],"osnova":"tu","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ",""],"osnova":"tvr","osnova2":"ava","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ",""],"osnova":"ure","osnova2":"aj","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ",""],"osnova":"ure","osnova2":"ivati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ",""],"osnova":"uspore","osnova2":"ivati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ",""],"osnova":"že","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
